Finding aid to the Classes of 1991-2000 records CA.MS.01028
Smith College Archives
Classes of 1991-2000 records
1984-2006
Smith College Archives
Smith College. Class of 1991.
CA.MS.01028
13.542 linear feet (25 containers)
College Archives has been collecting class material dating back to the Class of 1879. The Classes of 1991-2000 records consist of individual class notes, examinations, papers and class letters, correspondence, photographs, scrapbooks, songbooks as well as reunion materials of the same nature, all related to or dating from the time periods during which these classes were students at Smith College.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use with following restrictions on access: Box #'s 2301.3, 2301.4, 2301.5 - Closed until May 19, 2041 except to authors or with permission of Manja Sachet. Box #2302.3 - Closed until 2062
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Whenever donation information for a particular set of material is known, it is included in the finding aid below. However, a majority of the material was not formally accessioned and its origins are not currently known.
Arrangement
This collection brings together ten record groups that are arranged chronologically, one per graduating class. However, since some materials are placed in a class record group based on when they were created, and not by whom, materials relevant to a class may exist in more than one series.
Scope and Contents
The Classes of 1991-2000 records consist of individual class notes, examinations, papers and class letters, correspondence, photographs, scrapbooks, songbooks as well as reunion materials of the same nature, all related to or dating from the time periods during which these classes were students at Smith College.
Biographical / Historical
College Archives has been collecting class material dating back to the Class of 1879. Classes of 1991-2000 records combine the student material from those graduating classes into one record group.
Smith College -- Students.; Smith College -- Alumni and alumnae.; Smith College. Class of 1992.; Smith College. Class of 1993.; Smith College. Class of 1994.; Smith College. Class of 1995.; Smith College. Class of 1996.; Smith College. Class of 1998.; Smith College. Class of 1997.; Smith College. Class of 1999.; Smith College. Class of 2000.; Smith College -- Students.; Smith College -- Alumni and alumnae.
- Class of 1991 Records, 1987-1996; 2.667 linear feet (6 containers)
  Biographical / Historical
  The Class of 1991 was the 113th graduating class of Smith College.
  Scope and Contents
  The Class of 1991 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1991, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
  - General, 1990 (Box 2301, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1991 (Box 2301, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1991 (Box 2301, Folder 3)
  - Groups, 1987-1991 (Box 2301, Folder 4)
  - Ivy Day, 1991 (Box 2301, Folder 5)
  - Junior Ushers, 1990 (Box 2301, Folder 6)
  - Last Chapel, 1991 (Box 2301, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1993-1996 (Box 2301, Folder 8)
  - Sophomore Push, 1989 (Box 2301, Folder 9)
  - Who's Who, 1987 (Box 2301, Folder 10)
  - Yearbook, 1991 (Box 2301, Folder 11)
  - Yearbook Photographs (unprocessed)
    - Yearbook Photographs, 1991 (Box 2301.1, Folder 1)
    - Yearbook Photographs, 1991 (Box 2301.1, Folder 2)
    - Yearbook Photographs, 1991 (Box 2301.1, Folder 3)
    - Yearbook Photographs, 1991 (Box 2301.1, Folder 4)
    - Yearbook Photographs, 1991 (Box 2301.1, Folder 5)
    - Yearbook Photographs, 1991 (Box 2301.1, Folder 6)
    - Yearbook Photographs, 1991 (Box 2301.1, Folder 7)
  - Class Scrapbook, 1987-1991 (Box 2301.2)
  - Sachet, Manja correspondence, photos, writings, 1984-1992 (Box 2301.3)
  - Sachet, Manja - correspondence, photos, writings, 1984-1992 (Box 2301.4)
  - Sachet, Manja - journals, 1987-1991 (Box 2301.5)
- Class of 1992 Records, 1988-1997; 2.625 linear feet (4 containers)
  The Class of 1992 was the 114th graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1992 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1992, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - General, 1989-1992 (Box 2302, Folder 1)
  - Class Rep Meeting Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 2302, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1992 (Box 2302, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1992 (Box 2302, Folder 4)
  - Ivy Day, 1992 (Box 2302, Folder 5)
  - Junior Ushers, 1991 (Box 2302, Folder 6)
  - Last Chapel, 1992 (Box 2302, Folder 7)
  - Reunion Newsletter, 1997 (Box 2302, Folder 8)
  - Sophomore Push, 1990 (Box 2302, Folder 9)
  - Who's Who, 1988-1989 (Box 2302, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbooks, 1989-1990, 1990-1991 (Box 2302.1)
  - Class scrapbook (senior year), 1991-1992 (Box 2302.2)
  - Kurtz, Andrea - journals, correspondence, 1988-1992 (Box 2302.3)
- Class of 1993 Records, 1989-2003; 2.042 linear feet (4 containers)
  The Class of 1993 was the 115th graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1993 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1993, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - General, 1989-1995 (Box 2303, Folder 1)
  - Ada Comstock Scholars Photo Book, 1993 (Box 2303, Folder 2)
  - Class Rep List, 1993 (Box 2303, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, 1993 (Box 2303, Folder 4)
  - Ivy Day, 1993 (Box 2303, Folder 5)
  - Last Chapel, 1993 (Box 2303, Folder 6)
  - Reunion Newsletter, 1998-2003 (Box 2303, Folder 7)
  - Senior Ball, 1993 (Box 2303, Folder 8)
  - Sophomore Push, 1991 (Box 2303, Folder 9)
  - Who's Who, 1989-1990 (Box 2303, Folder 10)
  - Safford, Patricia May (Box 2304)
  - Class scrapbook - junior year, 1991-1992 (Box 2303.1)
  - Scrapbook (sophomore year), 1990-1991 (Box 2303.2)
- Class of 1994 Records, 1990-2004; 0.833 linear feet (2 containers)
  The Class of 1994 was the 116th graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1994 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1994, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Palucki, Laura Jean (Box 2305)
  - General, 1990 (Box 2306, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1994 (Box 2306, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1994 (Box 2306, Folder 3)
  - Groups, 1994 (Box 2306, Folder 4)
  - Junior Ushers, 1993 (Box 2306, Folder 5)
  - Class Newsletters, 1998 (Box 2306, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1996 (Box 2306, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1999 (Box 2306, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 2004 (Box 2306, Folder 9)
  - Who's Who, 1990-1991 (Box 2306, Folder 10)
  - Yearbook Photographs, 1994 (Box 2306, Folder 11)
- Class of 1995 Records, 1991-2004; 0.417 linear feet (1 container)
  The Class of 1995 was the 117th graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1995 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1995, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - General, 1991 (Box 2307, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1995 (Box 2307, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1995 (Box 2307, Folder 3)
  - Groups, 1995 (Box 2307, Folder 4)
  - Ivy Day, 1995 (Box 2307, Folder 5)
  - Junior Ushers, 1994 (Box 2307, Folder 6)
  - Last Chapel, 1995 (Box 2307, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters, 1997-2004 (Box 2307, Folder 8)
  - Senior Ball, 1995 (Box 2307, Folder 9)
  - Senior Pub Crawl, 1994 (Box 2307, Folder 10)
  - Sophomore Push, 1993 (Box 2307, Folder 11)
  - Who's Who, 1991-1992 (Box 2307, Folder 12)
- Class of 1996 Records, 1992-2006; 2.0 linear feet (2 containers)
  The Class of 1996 was the 118th graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1996 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1996, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - General, 1995-1996 (Box 2308, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1996 (Box 2308, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1996 (Box 2308, Folder 3)
  - Groups, 1993 (Box 2308, Folder 4)
  - Junior Ushers, 1995 (Box 2308, Folder 5)
  - Last Chapel, 1996 (Box 2308, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters, 1996-2002 (Box 2308, Folder 7)
  - Reunion, 2005-2006 (Box 2308, Folder 8)
  - Senior Ball, 1996 (Box 2308, Folder 9)
  - Senior Class Gift, 1996 (Box 2308, Folder 10)
  - Senior Newsletter, 1995-1996 (Box 2308, Folder 11)
  - Speeches and Remarks by Alison J. Wong, Senior Class President, 1995-1996 (Box 2308, Folder 12)
  - Sophomore Push, 1994 (Box 2308, Folder 13)
  - Who's Who, 1992-1993 (Box 2308, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook (Box 2308.1)
- Class of 1997 Records, 1993-2003; 0.833 linear feet (2 containers)
  The Class of 1997 was the 119th graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1997 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1997, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1997 (Box 2309, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1997 (Box 2309, Folder 2)
  - Groups, undated (Box 2309, Folder 3)
  - Junior Ushers, 1996 (Box 2309, Folder 4)
  - Last Chapel, 1997 (Box 2309, Folder 5)
  - Class Letters, 2003 (Box 2309, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1999 (Box 2309, Folder 7)
  - Sophomore Push, 1995 (Box 2309, Folder 8)
  - Who's Who, 1993-1994 (Box 2309, Folder 9)
  - Sinnreich, Helene - survey regarding Jewish life at Smith, November, 1996 (Box 2309.1)
- Class of 1998 Records, 1994-2004; 0.417 linear feet (1 container)
  The Class of 1998 was the 120th graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1998 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1998, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Christmas Vespers, 1997 (Box 2310, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1998 (Box 2310, Folder 2)
  - Last Chapel, 1998 (Box 2310, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters, 2004 (Box 2310, Folder 4)
  - Service of Remembrance, 1998 (Box 2310, Folder 5)
  - Sophomore Push, 1996 (Box 2310, Folder 6)
  - Who's Who, 1994-1995 (Box 2310, Folder 7)
- Class of 1999 Records, 1995-2000; 1.292 linear feet (2 containers)
  The Class of 1999 was the 121st graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1999 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1999, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Announcements, 1998-1999 (Box 2311, Folder 1)
  - Class Cabinet, 1998-1999 (Box 2311, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1999 (Box 2311, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1999 (Box 2311, Folder 4)
  - Convocation Address, 1999 (Box 2311, Folder 5)
  - Groups, 1998-1999 (Box 2311, Folder 6)
  - House Representatives, 1998-1999 (Box 2311, Folder 7)
  - Ivy Day, 1999 (Box 2311, Folder 8)
  - President's Files, 1996-1997 (Box 2311, Folder 9)
  - Rally Day, 1999 (Box 2311, Folder 10)
  - Reunion, 2000 (Box 2311, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook, 1997-1998 (Box 2311, Folder 12)
  - Senior Newsletter, 1998-1999 (Box 2311, Folder 13)
  - Who's Who, 1995-1996 (Box 2311, Folder 14)
  - Thanodokazi Mniki - photo album (Box 2311.1)
- Class of 2000 Records, 1996-2005; 0.417 linear feet (1 container)
  The Class of 2000 was the 122nd graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 2000 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 2000, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 2000 (Box 2312, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Speaker, 2000 (Box 2312, Folder 2)
  - Ivy Day, 2000 (Box 2312, Folder 3)
  - The New Student Record, 1996 (Box 2312, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters, 2001-2005 (Box 2312, Folder 5)
  - Paradise Found, 2000 (Box 2312, Folder 6)